Haw flakes...haw flakes!
山楂片   这是山楂片
It kinda looks like a rocket ship.
看起来像火箭飞船
No, it looks like a lantern.
不   它看起来像是一个灯笼
-No, it's a rocket ship, see? -No, Justin, a lantern that hangs from those strings.
-不   是火箭飞船   看到没   -不   贾斯汀   是挂在绳子上的灯笼
Oh, yeah! That's a better point.
哦   是  这个有说服力
I'm gonna eat one. I can't help it. These look good.
我想要吃一片   忍不住了   看起来很不错
They have like a strong lemon taste.
它们尝起来有股很强的柠檬味
Tastes like "sour patch kids"- the blue ones.
尝起来像酸酸片  蓝色的那种
Taste like cinnamon. No! Apple pie!
味道像肉桂   不   像苹果派
It's not apple, but it is from a fruit called the Chinese Hawthorn.
不是苹果   是一种叫山楂的东西
So you can pick candies off of the thorn bush.
所以你可以在荆棘丛里捡到糖果
I can't smell anything.
我闻不到任何味道
I don't like this smell.
我不喜欢这个味道
Oh, no!
哦   不
I've tried spicier, but this is still spicy!
我试过更辣的   不过这个还是很辣